The Point is a animation, family, fantasy film directed by Fred Wolf.
Years ago, there was a place called The Land of Point, because everything in The Land of
Point had one: the barns, the houses, the cars, everything, even the people.
Everyone in The Land of Point had a point at the top of its head.
Everyone, that is, except Oblio, who was born round-headed.
Since he had no point, Oblio, along with his trusty dog,
Arrow, was banished to the Pointless Forest.
Join them to see what wonders await these two intrepid travelers as they make
their way on their amazing, song-filled journey of discovery!
Narrator / Father (home video release) (voice), played by Ringo Starr.
Oblio's Father / Pointed Man's Right Head / King / Leaf Man
/ Villagers (voice), played by Paul Frees.
Count (voice), played by Lennie Weinrib.
Rock Man (voice), played by Bill Martin.
Count's Son (voice), played by Buddy Foster.
Oblio's Mother (voice), played by Joan Gerber.
Vanishing Point is a 1971 American action film directed by Richard C.
Sarafian, starring Barry Newman, Cleavon Little, and Dean Jagger.
It focuses on a disaffected ex-policeman and race car driver delivering a muscle car cross-country to California while
high on speed ("uppers" in the story), being chased by police, and meeting various characters along the way.
Since its release it has developed a cult following.
The film explores themes of narration, musical, outcast, dog.